- Tonight,
on "The Bachelorette"...
all: Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss!
[whooping]
- Whoo!
men: Hannah!
- Unconditional love--
that is what I'm looking for.
- Your, like, energy
is so, like, contagious.
- Newsflash:
Peter's my boyfriend.
- I'm at a place where I can
accept who I am
and give myself to someone,
and that's you.
- I feel something growing
inside me
that I've never felt before,
and I think it could turn into
forever.
- Oh!
- And now...
- No regrets.
Hold nothing back.
I'm gonna fight for her,
no matter what,
no matter how tired I am.
- You're violent.
You're aggressive.
You are a psychopath.
- Why does every single
guy here dislike you?
- We all know that Luke P.
is an evil,
pathological liar.
- Let me just tell you, man.
Karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
- Your story has changed.
I feel like you think
that I'm a threat to you,
'cause I am the biggest threat
against you right now.
- I'm not threatened
by anybody--
especially not you.
[siren wails]
- If somebody messes
with my queen,
I need to take
that person out.
- [sniffling, whimpers]
♪ ♪
[dramatic chords]
- It all starts right now.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- Cam--I think we all knew
that was happening.
- See you, Cam.
- I think it kind of proves
that guilt-tripping
your way into time with Hannah
isn't gonna go over well
for you or for anyone else,
so...
- Definitely.
- Can we just talk
about how good
Hannah looked last night?
- So good.
[laughter]
- What's up?
- Chris.
- Morning, boys.
- Morning.
- Morning, Chris.
- Room's getting smaller.
- Yeah.
- All right,
just 15 of you guys left.
Started with 30 and you guys
are the ones that made it.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- One thing that I've been
able to see
and I'm sure you guys have
noticed about Hannah as well,
whether it's Cam
or any other situation,
is like,
she handles her own.
Like, she takes
in the information
and then she takes care
of business.
And that's a good thing
to see,
and it should assure
you guys that,
you know, why she's here,
and she's serious about it.
- Yeah.
- Well, moving forward,
it's time to leave the mansion.
We're out of here.
- Ooh!
[all murmuring]
- Hey!
- Hannah's already left
Los Angeles.
- No way.
- Oh.
- It might be the smallest
state in the union,
but it's where the rich
and powerful play.
- Oh, I like it.
- You guys are heading
to Newport, Rhode Island.
[cheering]
You guys are wheels up
in an hour,
so go get packed,
'cause we're not coming back.
[cheering]
- Newport!
- Newport.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[cheering]
- Oh, yeah!
- We're here, baby!
We're here.
- We are at Gurney's Newport
Resort and Marina
in Rhode Island.
It's gorgeous here,
absolutely stunning,
super romantic vibes.
[cheering]
- Whoa!
- Let's check this view out
right here.
You guys see the bridge?
- The stakes are definitely
higher now.
We're out of the mansion,
we're in the final 15 guys,
so it'll be really interesting
to see what
Hannah has in store for us.
Hannah, where are you?
[laughs]
[birds squawking]
[knock at door]
- Date card.
[tense music]
all:
Ooh.
- There he is.
- Here we go.
♪ ♪
Jed...
- Oh!
- Meet me in Boston.
- Ooh.
If I had a tail,
I'd wag it for sure.
[laughter]
I'm ready to go.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I'm in Boston and I have
a hot date with Jed today.
First date of the week.
Don't know much about Boston
except that they threw
a bunch of tea
in some body of water.
There was a chant.
What was it?
No taxation,
no "represation"--
no representation...no.
No...without taxation.
"No taxation
without representation."
- I don't know,
I feel like it's close.
[laughs]
Hey!
- Hey.
- Glad you're here.
- I'm so glad to be here.
- Welcome to Boston.
- I know, it's amazing.
- Have you been here before?
- Never.
- Well...
- Where are we going?
What are we doing?
- We're just gonna
explore Boston together,
and I think we should start
at the Quincy Market.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
All right. Quincy Market.
- The Quincy Market
is our oyster.
[laughs]
I'm very excited to see Jed.
I've been wanting to have
one-on-one time with him
for a while,
because I feel like
this is actually somebody
that I could see myself with.
- I like it.
- Oh, my God, you look hot.
- Come on,
right this way, Miss.
[both humming jaunty tune]
- So, today's all about fun.
Fun in America.
I'm gonna make up a bunch
of random facts for you, okay?
- All right, perfect.
- This right here was
the Thomas Edison Hotel.
It was founded in 1692.
I love making up facts
about America.
I found that to be a new talent
of mine ten minutes ago.
Paul Revere invented the bike,
and this is the monument.
This is actually where
Benjamin Franklin did
his first interview.
This is where
Mr. Ronald McDonald got
his idea for the golden arches.
[laughs]
- Right.
- I always have so much fun
with Jed.
We are very relaxed
and comfortable together,
and I don't feel like I have
to be showboat-y around him.
I can just be Hannah.
It's a photo booth.
- We have to do it.
[in British accent]
- Do not come in here.
Oh.
- Three, two, one.
- [laughs]
[cheerful music]
One.
[laughter]
- I really like Jed,
and I don't think there's
anybody else that would
be better to have on this date.
I've been looking forward
to today a lot.
- Yeah?
- I don't think I could
do this date with just anyone.
Like, it has to be someone
that's, like, game,
can make jokes with me,
and just, like, shoot the bull.
And I love that about you.
- I like that about you too.
- I feel like
we're really comfortable.
- I know, I do too.
Like I said,
it's like the only time
when everything
kind of disappears,
and I'm just like
right here in this moment.
And I love that,
and honestly, I don't know
if I've ever had that ever.
- Really?
- I don't that I've ever had
like a moment
with someone where
it's just like everything else
kind of fades away,
which is special, I think.
- I think it is too.
- The day, so far, has been
one of my favorite days,
and it's been amazing
to just have, like,
a real date.
Hannah is beautiful
inside and out,
which is so important.
And she just makes me
really freaking happy,
and it's just like
an effort-less thing.
We're just both us
and it gels.
- I like being around you.
- I love being
around you.
So I'm looking forward
to seeing
what the rest of the day holds.
[all chanting]
Kiss! Kiss!
[overlapping shouting]
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
[bright music]
- Wonder what that monument is.
- Who knows?
You could just make it up
and say,
"I'm completely making
this up."
Today has been like
a crash course in Boston.
I really like Jed,
and I've been wanting
a one-on-one with him
for a while.
And I feel like this is
honestly the perfect
date for us.
We're just two southern people
joining together in love
to love on America
here in Boston.
Ice cream.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- Want some ice cream?
- Yes.
- Yes, please.
- [gasps]
Thank y--chocolate chip
cookie dough.
- It's your favorite.
- Birthday cake.
- Thank you so much.
- Have a good one.
- All right.
- Let's find a good spot.
- Cheers to our first
one-on-one that I've been
looking forward to
and making more history
than this town has to offer.
- And make it sweet.
- And make it real sweet.
[both laugh]
- Cheers.
- Mmm.
- I wanna try yours.
Mmm.
- Mmm.
I could eat this whole pint
right now.
Being with Jed feels natural,
like there's no pressure
to be perfect.
Everything just feels easy.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Today has been great,
and I have one last surprise
for Jed.
It's gonna be really fun.
- [sighs]
What are you getting me into,
Miss Hannah?
- Only fun.
[laughs]
- Oh.
All right.
- You ready?
- Yeah, I'm excited.
What's going on?
[gasps]
What?
[epic music]
Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Yo.
- What's up, Jaylen, Terry?
- Welcome to Boston.
- Hey!
- How you doing?
- Hi.
- What's up, man?
- Good to see you.
- I'm Jed, good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome to Boston, guys.
- Thank you.
- How's the date been?
How's you guys--
- How's it been?
- How's Boston?
- It's been awesome.
Boston's really cool.
- So you're getting along
with each other?
- I'm keeping him in shape.
- Keeping him in shape?
- She's keeping me in check
for sure.
- Speaking of that,
I'm gonna have you two guys
get suited up.
We got some stuff--
- Suited up?
- Yeah, we got some nice
jerseys for you guys.
- [gasps]
- Custom jerseys.
- Hannah B., this is for you.
- Oh, no way!
- Ah!
[laughs]
- Thank you.
- We'll give you all a few
minutes to get suited up.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I know.
Isn't that so cool?
These are sweet.
The Boston Celtics.
How is this a thing?
How is this real?
Scary Terry
and Jaylen Brown--
two of the best guys
in the league.
What?
[buzzer blares]
- Let's go two-on-two, baby.
- Split it up.
- I'm with Brown.
- Make it even.
- You know
my last name's Brown?
- I know.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
Oh, good pass.
Oh!
Yeah, turnover.
Here we go, yeah.
- Ah!
- Oh, good D!
You better not block it,
either.
You better let her score.
Right on that backboard.
Hey!
- Whoo!
Brown's never down!
- Hey, you got Terry to town.
- Brown's never down.
- Defense--the steal's
on him.
- Okay.
- Knock it down for game, Jed!
- Oh, my God.
- Yay, three!
- You know what?
This is the first time I've ran
in a hot minute.
- Ooh.
- No.
[screams]
- Whoo!
- Snuck one in.
- That's it?
Oh, there--no more cooties.
- Ooh.
No more points.
- [laughs]
- Let's do it.
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, Hannah.
Back 'em on down.
[overlapping shouting]
That's game.
- Yes!
I am the queen.
I am basketball champion.
I am a Celtic.
- So, tell me how everything
is going so far.
- Jed is awesome.
We have so much fun together.
He's very comforting
and funny and gentle.
- Okay.
- And a baller.
What do you think I should
look for in a man?
- Somebody that
makes you laugh.
Somebody who you can be
yourself with.
Somebody who respects you.
Somebody who's there
for the rough times
and the good times.
Somebody who's gonna accept
you for your flaws
and your beauty.
- I feel you.
That's what I've
been preaching.
- My girl.
- That was great.
- [laughs]
All right, guys,
appreciate you.
- All right, see you guys.
- You're awesome.
- Yeah, thank you.
You guys are too.
Appreciate it,
nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Let's play Love.
- Oh, I like that.
- You want to?
- Love, we're playing Love.
Okay.
- All right, you shoot first.
- I like that I don't have
to, like,
work at being with Jed--
it just is natural.
- Ooh.
Pressure's on.
- Oh.
It was really good
after last week
to come to a new place
and have time
with someone that
it's easy with.
- All right, this is the one.
This is the one.
[mellow guitar music]
- Oh!
[squeals]
♪ ♪
- I feel like today is what
Hannah and I both needed
to just, like,
assure each other that
there is something there.
Like, we both knew it,
but today just put it
all into reality.
I think it's just triggered
and exploded a spark
into a flame,
and now I think the only way
to go from here is up.
- Oh!
- [laughs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We don't know
what's gonna happen.
We all say that there's two
one-on-one dates
and one group date,
but the fact is,
there could be two group dates
following this.
We have no idea.
- Yeah.
- I'm hungry for my one-on-one.
- A one-on-one,
it would be amazing.
You know, I've been waiting
and hoping and wishing
for a while, you know.
[knock at door]
- Oh.
- Oh, boy.
- I think now it's like,
okay, we have
a strong relationship.
Let's have a one-on-one
and take that
next step forward.
- It's a group date.
Dylan,
Matteo,
John Paul Jones...
- [snickering]
- Connor,
Garrett,
Dustin,
Devin,
Grant,
Peter,
Kevin, Mike,
Luke S...
[suspenseful music]
Luke P.
"True love requires
blood, sweat, and tears.
Love, Hannah."
- There we go.
Got a date.
To get this one-on-one date,
I'm extremely stoked.
- I mean, my heart started
racing a little bit.
I'm thinking 'bout my name
might be called
for a one-on-one.
But boys, I'm excited.
You know, I'm a competitor,
so it's about to get bloody.
- This place is real nice.
I had so much fun today
with Jed.
It was just the best day
that I could have imagined.
[laughs]
And I feel excited about Jed.
- Oh...
This is so lovely.
- Isn't this so cool?
I'm excited to get to know
him more tonight.
He really is exactly what
I've wanted,
and I see that every single
time I'm with him.
- What was your favorite moment
of the day?
- With the Celtics,
when we were kissing
and you made the shot.
- Oh, that was nuts!
- That was really good.
- My favorite moment of the day
was when we got
in the photo booth
and we had that moment.
- Oh, yeah.
- And for a split second,
it was just us right there.
Even if it wasn't for long,
it was just like...
[sighs]
- Yeah.
- This is real.
I feel it.
I think that is just because
you're completely yourself.
It didn't take long
for me to just really know
that there was something here.
I hope you feel that way too.
- It means so much for you
to say that, honestly.
- Mm-hmm.
- And kind of opens up
the door for me
to be totally upfront,
and you've asked for nothing
but the truth this entire time.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's what you said day one.
I never really truly knew
how to say it,
but I just...music is like
my passion.
I want it more than anything
in this world.
It is...or has come natural to
me since I was this big
and I would go and, like,
sit next to my grandma
and just, like, be in awe
watching her play
and just watching her hands
go down those keys.
And I was like...
[sighs]
Even at the young age,
I was like, "I wanna do that."
It's something that I truly
and wholeheartedly love
with every bit of myself.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it's been really hard
and scary at times,
and it's made me question
if it's the right thing for me.
This is hard to talk about.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- But, um, when I signed up
for the show,
I was so clueless.
I was open to the idea,
'cause I love love.
- Mm-hmm.
- I do, I love the idea of it.
But my first thought was,
you know,
"This is like a huge platform."
- Mm-hmm.
- And I just want you to know
the truth.
So I came in with that mindset.
But every moment that we've had
has just kind of...
taken all that away
and showed me that, like,
now, more than anything,
I wanna be with you.
- I do really respect
that you're honest.
And I think, I truly think,
like, the passion that you have
for music is so amazing.
Like, I would never wanna take
that away from you.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I would never wanna
hinder that,
but I also know what I deserve
and what I need.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, how can you get from...
"I see this as an opportunity
for music"
to marriage?
Because that's why I'm here.
- Right.
So, um...
I have a hard time, like,
letting a wall down,
just because of, like,
past things.
- Yeah, me too.
- And you don't know
who you can be
open with and vulnerable.
But there's just a comfort
that comes from you,
and a lot of it's
in your voice.
I think a lot of it
is in your touch too.
And now that I see who you are,
that's all I want.
I feel something growing
inside me
that I've never felt before.
I'm starting to feel like
I'm falling for you
more and more.
And it's beyond a show
at this point,
because I know the only thing
that I would
really need is you.
- [whispers] Thank you.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
You're a really great guy.
I value your...
honesty with me.
I know that probably wasn't
easy to admit,
but in a way, it's exactly what
I've been asking for.
And I am catching feels,
and I'm super excited.
[laughs]
- I'm so excited.
- So, Jed, will you accept
this rose?
- One second.
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- I feel super lucky to have
Jed in this with me.
I love the passion we have
with each other,
and I am more excited
than I've been
in a long time
over a first date.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Today we fight!
- Whoo!
- I think it's important
to show Hannah
that I'm willing to fight
for her in this relationship.
- This is the kind of guy
who might hurt someone.
- Raaaah!
[crowd exclaiming]
[siren wailing]
- Oh, my God.
[sniffling]
- And then...
- You damn sure
won't go after me,
'cause I am the biggest threat
against you right now.
- I'm not threatened
by anybody,
especially not you.
- You gonna grab somebody,
come after me, homie.
- Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa--
- Oh, God [bleep]!
[solemn fanfare]
♪ ♪
[cheers]
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
Hello!
Ah!
Don't hurt me.
Hey!
Ah!
[Hannah laughs,
overlapping chatter]
- Hey.
How are y'all?
Hey.
Hey, guys.
all: Hey.
- Welcome to Rhode Island.
You like it so far?
- Yeah!
- Are y'all ready for some
blood, sweat, and tears today?
all: Yes.
- I am.
[laughter]
So let's go.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
- This is gonna be
the most competitive
group date we've had.
You know, 13 guys.
We're all starting
to develop feelings.
It's gonna be tough,
but at the end of day,
Hannah's worth it.
So, blood, sweat, and tears,
I'm ready.
[all grunting]
all:
Oh!
- Rugby!
- Oh, God [bleep]!
- Oh...
[laughs]
- Oh.
- Ooh!
- The blood, sweat, and tears
couldn't be
a more accurate statement.
I know rugby's
a pretty gruesome sport.
[man grunting]
So it'll be, uh...
it'll be--it'll be rough.
[men groaning]
- Oh!
- I've never played rugby
in my life,
but I've played high school
football, so I've gotten
a little taste of what it's
like to be a little physical.
So I'm looking forward
to this--I'm excited.
- Welcome, gentlemen,
to Fort Adams.
This is the home
of the Newport Rugby Club.
We're the reigning
New England Rugby champs.
Difference between
rugby and American football:
no helmets, no pads...
it's you, your mouthpiece,
and a pair of cleats.
- There's no timeouts.
There's no water breaks.
It's a full contact sport,
boys.
Somebody's getting smashed
every minute in this game.
We see some gruesome stuff
out on this field
and we've seen people
knocked unconscious,
seen people breaking
their legs,
legs hanging off, only being
held on by skin and sock.
You get smashed, you stand up
and you smash somebody,
and that's how you play rugby.
- Boys ready to play
some rugby?
- Let's go!
Let's go, boys!
Let's go!
- Attack!
[laughs]
- Hit it, hit it, hit it!
- Ground your legs.
Nice legs.
Go to ground!
♪ ♪
Nice...good!
Go to ground.
Get me that ball.
- Oh!
This is awesome!
I want a manly-man
who's not afraid
to get down and dirty.
I mean, this is so hot.
Mm-mm.
[laughs]
Oh, do I just go?
- Yeah!
- Say, like, "Go."
- Go.
- Hannah Beast!
- Aaaaaah!
- Get the ball back, Hannah.
Yeah, get the ball back!
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah!
Today will be really physical,
mentally and physically tough,
but I don't want anybody
truly to get hurt today.
My number one priority is
for everyone to have fun
and to be safe.
Grab him up!
Bottom up!
[cheers]
- Rugby--you gotta be
friggin' tough
to play this game.
- Whoo!
- There it is!
- It's probably one
of the most intense things
I've ever seen.
We're gonna get a little game
going on here pretty soon,
and it's gonna get interesting.
[tense music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Whoo-hoo!
Feeling good.
- One, two, three.
all: Blood, sweat, tears!
- Whoo!
- Today, we fight!
- Today, they die!
- Whoo!
- Let's go!
- Hannah on three, men,
let's go!
One, two, three.
all: Hannah!
- [screams]
[laughs]
Ah, yeah, let's go, man.
[indistinct].
[traditional Celtic music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- First rugby game ever
in Newport, Rhode Island
in front of over 1,000 people
with our girl Hannah watching.
Whoo!
I'm ready for it.
- Let's go, let's go,
let's go!
- This is cool--it is like
the craziest thing.
Like, we're in a coliseum
completely surrounded by fans
just, like, cheering
and going crazy.
This is literally, like,
the most epic game
I've ever played, so I just--I
can't wait to get on the field.
- I want blood!
all: I want Blood!
- Sweat!
all: Sweat!
- And tears!
all: Tears!
- Play ball!
[cheering]
- I'm fighting for Hannah!
Baby, let's go!
[crowd cheering]
- There you go, Peter!
- [grunts]
- Oh.
Oh, God.
- Somebody pick it up
and go.
- Yeah!
[screams]
- [grunting]
- Go, go, go!
[cheers and applause]
- There you go, boys!
That was pretty good!
Whoo!
[whistle blows]
- We gotta scrum down.
We got a knock on.
We're gonna have a scrum.
- Scrum down!
- Let's go, boys!
- Come on, boys!
- [pants]
- [spits]
- [breathing heavy]
- Go.
[all grunting]
- Whoo!
[screams]
[crowd chanting]
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him!
- [grunting]
[cheering]
- [groaning]
- [jeering]
- Yee-hoo!
[all cheering]
- Oh!
[whistle blows]
- Halftime, boys.
Halftime.
- I can't lift my shoulder.
Can I just get it looked at?
Just it's [bleep] killing me.
- Okay.
Can we get the medic for Kevin,
please?
- Yeah.
Oh.
I think I literally dislocated
my shoulder.
It's just pain to lift up.
- That's there--[bleep].
- Oh, my gosh.
- Okay.
- What's wrong?
- No, just going
for the tackle,
I think I literally landed
on my shoulder wrong.
- We're gonna take him
to Newport.
He's gonna need some X-rays.
[dramatic music]
You're doing good, bud.
Thank you, man.
Thanks for being a trooper.
Yeah, it's swollen up here.
- Oh, [bleep]!
- I didn't see what happened,
but Kevin had
some shoulder injury.
I think he just fell on it
the wrong way
making a tackle,
and that's what did it for him.
- [sighs]
- Hopefully everything's okay.
- Yeah--
- Aw...
- I wanted them to give
their all
and be tough and tackle,
but of course
I don't really wanna see
anybody get hurt.
I'm just really hopeful
that Kevin will be okay.
- Kevin's leaving.
[siren wails]
- Kevin went to the hospital.
You know, I felt
kind of bad for him.
But this is all for Hannah,
and Hannah's
the true motivation,
so I'm gonna fight for her
no matter what,
no matter how tired I am.
When this is all
said and done,
everyone will see
what kind of fight
I bring to the table.
[cheers and applause]
[whistle blows]
- We're out there playing
for Hannah,
so I think we definitely
gave her
what she was asking for--
blood, sweat, and tears.
- [grunting]
[cheers and applause]
- [panting]
[whistle blows]
You know, I'm giving it
all I got for Hannah.
I refuse to quit.
I'll never quit on her.
[grunts]
- Uh--no.
[whistle blows]
It's okay.
- I think it's important
to show Hannah
that I'm willing
to fight for her
in this relationship.
[whistle blows]
- Oh!
- Oh, there you go, Garrett.
[crowd yelling]
- Go, go, go!
[exciting music]
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Hey, that was awesome.
- Thank you.
- Oh, come on, Garrett.
Whoo!
- I'm so proud of our team.
I think we did
a really good job
showing our true colors
and showing our teamwork.
Playing sports in general,
playing competitively
will show
someone's true character.
- Yes!
Whoo!
- [panting]
[whistle blows]
- Here we go, boys.
[cheers and applause]
[exciting music]
- Go.
Oh!
- [grunts]
[crowd groaning]
- Luke P.,
the guy's a beast,
and he's super aggressive,
but I think
maybe sometimes he can be
a little too aggressive.
[crowd cheering]
- I think the words,
"blood, sweet, and tears"
might have been taken
just a little bit
too literally.
[men grunting]
- This is the kind of guy
who might like, God forbid,
might, like, you know,
hurt someone.
- Come on, Connor!
- Hey!
[men grunting]
[crowd groans]
[whistle blows]
- That's game, guys.
- Did you see what happened?
- Luke and Luke went at it.
- What happened?
- Oh, they just tackled--
- But who, like--
- I have no idea.
- You gotta put your team
in the best position to win.
I'm trying my best to play
within the rules of the game,
but I'm playing rugby,
you know.
This is like football.
It's a contact sport.
- That was fun, man.
- Hey, Luke.
Hey.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to tell you
I'm sorry.
That was self-defense.
- Luke can't control himself,
frickin' animal.
I mean, it's just crazy
to see--I've never seen
anything like it before
in my whole life.
I think at this point,
it's safe to say that
in competitive situations,
he poses a threat
to other people.
You guys didn't see what
just happened back there?
- What happened?
- Yeah, what happened?
- He [bleep] decked me
out of nowhere.
Luke.
He body slammed me, dude.
- Don't worry about it.
- Hey.
It's about how you respond
to it, all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm good, I'm good.
- Don't worry,
that's his problem.
It's not yours.
- I know, I know.
- Luke P.,
he's just kind of a [bleep].
I think he wants to stand out.
He wants to continue
to puff his chest out
in a lot of different ways.
- Yeah, I saw him
when he got up.
He kneed you right
in the face.
- He kneed me in the face.
- He kneed you in the face?
- Yeah.
- Luke P. is only looking out
for Luke P.
Luke S. did nothing
that deserved retaliation.
He truly did not.
- [exhales]
- I'm not worried about it.
I told him I'm sorry,
he doesn't wanna talk to me,
I get it.
- He tried to play it off
as self-defense, dude.
I mean, give me a break.
You know,
he's so full of [bleep],
that it's like, it's coming
out of his ears, you know?
I really hope Hannah saw that.
I'm gonna tell her.
I'll tell her about it.
I'll tell her what happened.
- Hey, bro,
can we talk a little bit?
- No.
- No?
- Nope.
He's an unstable guy.
He shouldn't be here.
[tense music]
- Whoo!
- I just never
wanna see him again,
and I hope I don't see
much more of him.
[dramatic chords]
- Coming up...
- You know everyone in here
thinks you're nuts, right?
You misinterpreted
that situation completely.
- I'm a competitor, and I'm
gonna do everything I can
to fight for Hannah's heart.
You know, I don't want
to talk about him,
but to be honest,
at the house and everything,
I've seen red flags come up.
- He said that
you don't really talk about me.
- I'm pissed off.
Luke P. is a malicious guy
who will say anything
to save his own skin.
I'm here for Hannah,
and don't you ever forget it.
It makes me so angry that
I have to defend myself
over some garbage fed to her
by some psychopath.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Today with Hannah,
we had a good time,
but there was an incident.
Luke P. made a unsportsmanlike
play with Luke S.
- The point of today was
for Hannah to see us
in a different environment
and to see how we interact
with each other as teams.
I think some people
went overboard.
- Luke P. just acted like
a complete maniac today.
Doesn't surprise me,
because we've seen a pattern
with Luke P.
- And there she is.
- Ooh.
- Hey.
- Wow.
- This is a weird night.
Luke P. overstepped
a line today,
especially at the rugby game.
I think Hannah knows
what she's doing,
but I just hope
she doesn't get played,
at the end of the day.
- Well, I had a good time
today,
and like to see you all
get after it.
Unfortunately,
Kevin's not here,
because he got a little
banged up today.
He's in the hospital.
We think he's doing okay.
But I am really excited
to continue
to get to know you all.
So Luke P...
- Yes?
- You wanna go and talk?
- Yes, I would love to.
- Yeah, let's go.
[tense music]
- Luke P. body slammed me
in a little rugby match.
The guy's a lunatic.
- Okay, in this room
right here.
- I don't trust a guy
like that.
I don't know what he says
to her in private.
I don't know what she buys
and what she doesn't buy,
and that is actually a really
scary, terrifying thing.
- How are ya?
- I'm great.
- Yeah?
- How are you doing?
- I'm doing...
I'm doing good.
- Um, yeah, today,
I don't know if you noticed,
but Luke S. and I had
an encounter on the field.
I had the ball, I stiff-armed
him to the ground.
But, you know, he started,
like, cussing me out
and, like, clenched his fists
and started coming at me
and started to swing at me,
like, to hit me in the face.
And I didn't know what to do,
and I, like, picked him up
and, you know, I put him
on his back.
And I'm really--I'm doing
my best after the last thing--
the conversation we had
about all of this.
- Yeah?
- I've been really trying hard.
- My emotions with you
are high,
and it's because I do
really care about you,
and I want to feel confident
in my feelings toward you.
But then when I hear things
like that,
it, um, just worries me
a little bit.
- I genuinely apologize,
'cause I don't want you to have
to--especially with me,
I don't want you to have
to think twice
about my character
and who I am as a person
and things like that.
- Hmm, okay.
Um...
do you feel--have you had
any other instances
with other guys in the house?
- Not at all.
Luke's been the only one
from the start
who's like always been
short with me and avoided me.
You know, I don't wanna talk
about him, you know,
to be honest, at the house
and everything,
I've seen red flags come up.
- Well, tell me.
- Like, he's always talking
about his brand
and his liquor company,
and I've never heard him
talk about you.
You know, Hannah,
I am crazy about you.
And if anything, my feelings
have grown stronger.
And I just want you to know,
like, I've told you nothing
but the truth,
and I'm gonna continue--
- 1,000% honest?
- Yes.
I would never lie to you.
- Don't, like, beat around
the bush, though, too.
- At all...
- Because that will
make me mad.
- About any details.
- I hear you,
and I do respect you,
but I need to, like,
think about it
for a little while.
Okay?
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
- I don't know what to think.
It's very obvious that Luke P.
is passionate about
whatever he does,
whatever he's going after.
And at that point,
it was winning a game,
and Luke S. pissed him off,
I guess.
I don't know.
Luke, you wanna go talk?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Cool.
I definitely have to have
a conversation
with Luke S.,
because I'm very confused
about, like, who did what.
[sighs]
- You okay?
You good?
- Yeah, um...
- Yeah?
- It was very obvious
there was some tension
on the field today.
I wanna know, like,
what the deal is
with you and Luke.
- Yeah, today was really tough
for me.
- Mm-hmm.
- There was a play
where I had passed the ball
and Luke hit me
pretty damn hard.
And I walked up to him
and he turned around
and he had this glazed look
in his eye.
And I just wanted to say
to him,
"Hey, man, like, I didn't
appreciate you doing that."
But instead, he picked me up
and he threw me down
on the ground,
knocked the wind out of me
and then kneed me in the head
and then walked away.
- Um, I did talk to Luke P.,
and he said that
you've kind of been a little
frustrated with him.
- I think a lot of us are
pretty irritated with Luke P.
A lot of us are.
The fact that he said
he was falling in love with you
after, you know, how long
of knowing you...
- Mm-hmm.
- A day or two?
We were all kind of like
looking at each other funny,
like, "Could that be possible?"
And then the next group date,
he talked about throwing
in the towel
and then saying that
"Hannah's not interested
in me anymore.
I'm thinking about leaving."
So that ticked us all off.
Then today, he body-slams me.
Listen, I don't know
all the stories.
I would urge you to ask
the other guys about it.
- Mm-hmm.
- So when you say that
I had "a thing" with Luke P.,
we all have a thing
with Luke P.
♪ ♪
- Uh, there was one other
thing that he said
that did bother me.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- He said that, you know,
you don't really talk about me
and that you really talk
a lot about
your tequila brand.
♪ ♪
I mean, that's concerning,
'cause I mean...
- That's just not true.
I understand how big
of a concern that is for you.
- Yeah.
- But I am here for you.
Seriously, I like you,
and I'm serious about that.
- Thank you.
- Like, that really
makes me upset
to hear that.
Um...
- I appreciate you for giving
me all the information
that you can.
I'm gonna use my time
to, like, understand
what's going on.
So, thank you.
- Luke P. felt the need
to tell Hannah
that I was here to promote
my tequila business,
which isn't even
a business yet.
It was awful to know
that she could
potentially believe him
and then wanna
end things with me
because of it.
And I hope that tonight
Hannah has conversations
with all the other
great guys here
and truth really comes out.
- Today was rough.
The end of the day.
- The only thing I did see
is when Luke P.
did throw Luke S. down.
- Mm-hmm.
- And kneed him in the face.
- I don't know if it was
intentional or not, do you?
- It was intentionally
just rough play.
Unfair play, and I feel like
it was definitely bullying,
what he did.
- I'm really irritated
and worried
I misjudged.
- Luke P. has 100% said
to my face,
"I think I'm gonna tell her,
Mike, that I'm starting
"to fall out of love with her.
I think that I'ma quit
the show."
That's what the boy said.
- It's not just Luke S.
that has issues with Luke P.
There are a lot of men
in the house
that are frustrated with him.
- I mean, the first night,
I thought Luke P. was
a little off.
There's a reason
95% of the guys in the house
don't get along with him.
- It's one thing,
the physicality in rugby,
it's another thing
if everyone doesn't like him.
It makes me really question
our relationship a lot.
- Like Hannah said herself,
this isn't the Luke P. show,
but it's annoying
that we have to continue
to talk about Luke P.
when we all are here
for a relationship with her
and the fact that Luke P.
has obviously shown
that he is here for
the wrong reasons.
It's annoying.
- Kevin, how you doing, man?
- I'm good, much better.
- What's the diagnosis?
- Sprained "agnioclaviculous"
joint.
- Let's hit the elephant
in the room here.
Luke, I've got 14 friends
in this house,
and you could have
seriously hurt one today.
I'm gonna let you know
that I'm not okay with that.
- For the third date, we have
made it [bleep] about you.
That is pissing me
the hell off.
Hannah told your ass last week
to stop making this about you.
You're taking up
my [bleep] time
with the woman
I'm trying to get to know.
- [scoffs]
- You laugh because
you're a [bleep] psychopath.
You know?
- Okay.
I wanna explain myself,
because you guys didn't see
what happened today
with your own eyes.
So, look, this whole
sideline scuffle...
I don't remember
how it happened,
to be completely honest
with you.
I think I had the ball.
I'm pretty sure
I stiff-armed him.
While he was on the ground,
he's cussing me
and he's coming up to me
with clenched fists
and he is marching towards me.
I felt like I needed
to defend myself.
- I was not gonna
punch you in the face, Luke.
I'm not that kind of person.
That's ridiculous,
and I'm pissed off to hell
that you think
that I would do that.
- So why would everybody else
tell us another story
than what you just told us?
- I just told you guys--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
I'm not finished yet.
- Finish.
- So you just said,
"Oh, well, I pushed him down.
"He was on the ground
and started cussing me
with clenched fists."
This is all after you said
you don't remember
what happened.
- Now that
you're telling me that,
I remember now, because--
- Oh, get the [bleep]--
Oh, my God!
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm feeding back through
my memory.
No, no, no.
- Luke.
- Let me finish.
I remember, 'cause I did
stiff-arm him to the ground.
- Can we just--
- I can't take this [bleep]
anymore, baby.
I can't take this [bleep].
- He tried blocking me.
You don't block in rugby.
That's not childish at all.
[dramatic music]
They want to freak out
and blow out of proportion
me being physical
on a rugby field.
I'm a competitor,
and I'm gonna do everything
I can to fight
for Hannah's heart.
No regrets,
hold nothing back.
You know, when it comes
to my relationship
with Hannah,
I'll never quit on her.
[dramatic end chords]
[dramatic music]
[knocking]
- Hey.
- Hannah.
- What's up?
- Nothing much.
How you doing?
- I'm good.
How about you?
- Doing great.
- Night's going
a little crazy.
Hannah's really
struggling tonight.
It's turned from
a night about Hannah
into a night about Luke P.
It's not gonna be
the Luke P. show.
You know, I've got something
that's really tugging at me
that I want to tell her
and it's gonna take
her mind off everything.
Remember, I'm the guy
that fell flat on my face
trying to score a touchdown
on the sideline today.
- I thought you played great.
Was I watching
a different game?
- Hey, it was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
- Yeah, it was--it was good.
- But I did want to tell
you something.
- Okay.
- I'm crushing for you hard.
- [laughs]
- Straight up.
And I wanted
to let you know that.
'Cause in the past
being vulnerable
has been uncomfortable for me.
And honestly just hearing
myself say that
is a little uncomfortable
for me now,
but that's--that's
totally okay, you know?
- Garrett, Garrett, Garrett.
I have been just trying to get
you to just be open with me.
But I needed you
to say something,
so I really appreciate
you saying something.
[light music]
♪ ♪
My relationship with Garrett
is definitely growing.
And he told me he has
a crush on me.
And I love that.
That was so sweet.
I really am excited to see
where our relationship
goes in this.
We didn't talk about
any of the drama at all.
And I really appreciated that.
♪ ♪
- You know everyone in here
thinks you're nuts, right?
How do you feel about that?
- Well, I--I know I'm not.
I'm just telling the truth.
- You're giving me that same
glazed look you gave me
today in the field.
It's a little terrifying,
but I'll be all right.
Why did you deck me?
Why did you body-slam me
in front of that crowd?
- I genuinely thought you were
starting to swing at me.
- You misinterpreted
that situation completely.
And I am actually extremely
pissed off at you.
I am here for Hannah.
And don't you ever
[bleep] forget it.
It makes me so angry that I had
to sit in there with the woman
that I really, really like
and defend myself
over some garbage fed
to her by some psychopath.
I never want to see you
again in my life.
Seriously.
[tense music]
- Okay, well, I really hope
that you turn around
and I would love to continue
to get to know you on a more
real and deeper level,
'cause, man,
all I've done is try
to be cool with you.
All I've done is respect you.
- Yep.
I cannot wait till you're
tossed off this show.
♪ ♪
[bleep] that guy.
Seriously.
He's, in fact, a liar
who will say anything
to save his own skin.
And he fed it to Hannah,
and you know what?
He's gonna get
what's coming to him.
- It was a very fun day.
- It was a really fun day.
- It was good.
- Overall, so fun.
- You know what
I love about you?
- What?
- Is just, like, your, like,
energy and your, just, like--
your outlook on life is so,
like, contagious
and I don't know.
You just make me feel so good.
And it's rare.
Like, you are
a very special girl.
And I feel like, honestly,
like one of the luckiest guys
in the world
to even be here.
- And you should know that I
feel really good about us, too,
so all your feelings are valid.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- But can you handle
when I'm not positive
and I'm just a bitch?
'Cause that happens.
- I get that and obviously
life's not always perfect.
And, like, you know there's
gonna be times where
a partner has to pick
the other one up.
But, you know, I think if you
laid a solid foundation down
and, I don't know,
you find the right person,
you know,
it's amazing when you do.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you can always
be there for each other.
And I'm very, very excited
for where this can go.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
Hannah is everything
that I've ever wanted.
♪ ♪
I am so just focused on her
and I'm so excited about her.
Like, I feel butterflies
every time I'm with her.
And I love that.
And I'm just feeling
really good right now.
Obviously I'm really hoping
for a rose to keep this going
because I see it going far.
- [sighs]
Tonight's been really
difficult for me.
And, um, I do appreciate every
conversation I had tonight.
I appreciate y'all just
sticking with me
while I struggle a little bit.
Um, one of you really took
the time to open up
and, um, be vulnerable
in their own way.
So, Garrett, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
[laughs]
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- I appreciate it.
Bye, y'all.
- Good night.
♪ ♪
- Tonight coming off
of all the drama,
my head was just full
of questions.
My mind feels like mush.
And so it's hard and exhausting
and I'm so tired
in every single way.
I don't know where
I'm at right now.
And it's stressing me out.
♪ ♪
[ship horn blares]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffles]
[sighs]
I'm just struggling
with my emotions today.
[sniffles]
Last night was just
a constant state
of frustration and confusion
about Luke P.,
and it's very obvious that
I have feelings for him...
probably the strongest.
And I don't know if
I'm reading him wrong or right.
[sniffles]
But I just, like,
see a potential there,
and I just, like, am mad
if I can't even trust myself
with, like, my feelings.
It's just really hard.
'Cause I want to.
Like, I want to have
a good date with Tyler C.
and just focus
on Tyler C. today.
Like, I--that's what I want.
[sniffles]
Like, truly,
that's what I want.
But, like, I don't know
right now if I can.
[groans]
[sniffles]
Honestly, I don't want to
talk to anybody.
Uh...
Because I'm just not
all right today.
[sniffles]
[whimpers]
[seagull cawing]
[bell ringing rhythmically]
[boat motor rumbling]
- What's up, girl?
How are you?
- I'm okay.
- What's good?
- [laughs]
What's good?
- How are you?
Mm!
- [squeals]
- So happy to see you!
- Let's sit down.
- Wow, beautiful day.
- It is.
- Beautiful day.
Has nothing on you, though.
- [laughs]
You're sweet.
- What's going on?
- Wanna sit here?
- Yeah, let's sit.
So how are you?
- Um...
Sorry.
The wind's in my hair.
- That's all right.
- Um...
I am honestly not that great.
- Yeah.
Rough night?
- Yeah, and I didn't have the
best morning,
so, um...
Like, last night
was just a lot.
I know I'm supposed to be here,
but sometimes I'm like,
I don't know why.
And if it's gonna work.
Um...
- Come here.
I'm here for you.
- I want today to be fun.
I'm just, like, not, like,
that fun right now.
So I'm really sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
- Um...
- Look at me.
We're gonna have fun
regardless, all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- We'll make the most of it.
I got you.
Don't worry, all right?
- I know.
Um...
- I mean, just--just know
that when you're getting down,
there's a reason why you're
going through all this
right now.
There's no doubt
in my mind that
this is all gonna make you
better at the end of the day,
and you're gonna come out
the most amazing person ever.
And with the most amazing
person ever.
- I didn't want to be
like this today, so--
- No, but I want you
in your highs
and I want you in your lows,
you know?
I'll take, you know,
whatever I can get with you.
You know?
That's what I want.
I want to be the man
next to you
at the end of this,
you know?
And I think today I want to
show you
that I can be that guy
that picks you up.
We're gonna have fun,
and that's what we're gonna do,
you know?
So let me just--
there's that smile.
There's--there's a little bit
of a ray there.
There--there it is.
We'll have fun.
And just know I got you.
And I'm always gonna have you,
regardless.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
Look how pretty that is.
- Wow.
That's beautiful.
I've been waiting and hoping
and wishing
for my shot
for the one-on-one.
Her being emotional,
like, showed me
how real she's taking this
and how hard
this can be for her.
And I want her to know
who I'm here for,
and it's on me
to pick her up,
keep her laughing
and keep her smiling,
make her forget
about yesterday.
- I've got some
lobster traps here.
You guys ready?
- Yeah.
- The first trap is right there
waiting for us.
- Oh, that little buoy?
- Oh, yeah, that buoy's
attached to a trap down there.
If you want to just
pull it in and--
- Oh, pull it in?
There you go.
Stop getting lost in my eyes,
okay?
- [laughs]
- Just focus on
what we're doing here.
- Shut up.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- There we go.
Perfect.
- Think we got something?
- Hope so.
- Feeling lucky.
Uh-oh.
- This is so beautiful.
- Here we go.
Look at that.
- Oh, we got some!
Yay!
- Pull that in.
- We got a keeper.
- What a catch.
- What--
[laughter]
You're a great catch.
♪ ♪
- I think we got this.
We make quite a team.
- Oh, I got it.
- There you go.
Beautiful.
[grunts]
Uh-oh, we got something big,
it sounds like.
[water burbling]
- Yay!
- Pull that in.
Oh, yeah, look at that one.
- Now twist.
Pull up.
[crunch]
Oh.
[laughter]
Oopsie.
- There you go.
- I'm a fisherman.
- [chuckles]
Hannah's going through
a lot.
But I hope I got her
back at ease
and feeling good about
everything that's going on.
- Whoo! Whoo!
- Beautiful. We're crushing it.
- End of the day, she's gonna
go through things in life
and I'm gonna go through
things in life,
and it's on us
to pick each other up.
And today meant the world
to be able to just sit there
and just be us and kind of
put all the pressure
and all that stuff aside.
♪ ♪
- This is freakin' awesome.
- Yep.
- Ooh, yeah.
Butter me up, girl.
- [laughs]
- How is it?
Want some tail?
For us to just kind of still
have the day that we did and,
you know, shows a lot
about our compatibility.
It shows that
we can be together
and get through tough times.
[laughter]
It's amazing, you know?
And it's great to have that
feeling with somebody.
♪ ♪
Yeah, it was awesome.
- Do you cook?
- Yeah, I can whip it up
a little bit.
- I'm pretty tough
about my steaks.
- Are you?
- You think I would approve?
- Yeah, big-time.
Big-time griller.
- Okay.
- Big-time chiller.
[laughter]
I'm really glad
that I didn't let,
you know, all my emotions
get in the way
of the fun today.
Tyler was so patient
and comforting all day.
It was really nice.
- You good?
- Mm-hmm.
- Having fun?
- Good.
- I'm just very calm.
And that's good.
- That's good.
I'm glad.
Nowhere else I want to be
right now.
- Thank you.
I'm so happy.
- You were amazing today.
And I loved every bit of it.
- I needed this today.
I do care for Tyler,
and I appreciate
him being here
and making me feel special.
♪ ♪
[gentle music]
- Let's have a night.
- Let's do it.
Wow.
- I think Tyler really was
good for me today.
I was upset about things
from last night,
but I will say, like, he was
there and comforted me all day.
It was really sweet.
Thank you.
Isn't this nice?
- Beautiful.
- It's the oldest tavern
in America.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Every time that he talks to me,
he makes the most of it.
And I mean, I still want to
learn more about him,
so I am really excited about
our relationship
moving forward.
- You are crushing your outfit
once again.
You are looking amazing.
- Hey, I gotta show up.
- You're dangerous in black.
So--
- That's how I like it.
- All right.
- On the edge.
- Today was a good day.
- A really good day.
- You know,
and, you know, I love
that I was able to be the one
to be able to pick you up.
You know?
It meant a lot to me.
And I was glad I could show you
I can do that.
- I was really excited
that it was you today.
- Yeah?
- Because
there are not many people
that could have made me
feel comforted today.
I'm thankful for you.
- Yeah, well...
I mean, I'm glad I could be
that guy.
- Yeah?
- You know, sometimes you
need a man to stand up for you
and fight for you
and--or sometimes
talk you off a ledge.
You know, like, "Relax.
Like, we'll--you know,
we'll get through this."
You know?
- Yeah.
- That's why, like,
we have each other.
And that's what it's all about.
We're not always gonna be
super chipper and--
- Yeah, that's hard for me
here, though.
- Exactly.
- Because, like, I want to give
this all, like, my very best.
And be, like, the best Hannah.
I just, like, I can't be.
- We don't--
but we don't need the best.
We need the real Hannah.
- I know.
- And I got that today.
And I adored that today.
- I honestly feel so bad
because I was like a little--
wasn't sure about you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, to be completely blunt,
like, I was--I thought you
were like a little player.
And I was like, hmm.
Okay.
Like, why are you here?
And, like, it really did, like,
make me want to
put a wall up with you.
Coming into it,
like,
what were your intentions?
Like--
- No. No, I get--I know.
It's an important question
for you.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think I'm really at a point
where I'm really
accepting of who I am
and ready to give myself
to somebody else.
- Mm-hmm.
- To be honest, I almost,
like, didn't come here.
I almost stepped away.
There was, uh--
Oh, man.
My pops almost died, like, two
months before I came out here.
- God.
- He got really sick, and
he was in the hospital
like 25 days.
He was in a coma
for, like, ten days.
It was--it was tough.
Like, I mean, I had to
sign away his rights
and sit and wait for surgery.
- You did?
- Yeah.
It was a tough--it was, like,
the hardest thing
I ever went through
in my life, you know?
I really didn't even
want to come, you know?
But then, like, my pops
kind of started to recover.
Had a successful surgery.
You know,
every day I'm with him
just doing everything I can
to make him better and--
you know, me and my dad
would sit around
and watch "The Bachelorette."
And he kind of, like,
became a huge fan
of you, you know?
And he was like, "Ty,
this is your girl.
You gotta go make the most of
this opportunity."
And so I went for it,
and I'm still feeling like,
"Ah, I don't know
if this is for me."
- Mm-hmm.
- And then,
you know,
I get to the limo,
and I see you.
I got this feeling that
I've never had for someone.
- You did that.
You went--
- Yeah.
- I remember.
- Yeah, I had this feeling
for someone
that I've never felt
for someone before,
you know what I mean?
And that confirmed a lot for me
right then and there.
I was like, "I'm not here
for 'The Bachelorette.'
I'm here for Hannah."
You know?
- I just want you to know
that, like,
I appreciate you sharing that.
It just makes sense hearing
how you were with your dad
and then, like, today with me.
- Yeah.
- You really did
rise to the occasion and
give me the comfort
that I needed.
- I'll take you any way I
can get you.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- And if I gotta pick you up,
I'll be happy to pick you up.
- So is your dad okay now?
- Yeah, he's doing well.
- Okay.
- He's a fighter.
He's kind of made me
the fighter I am today.
Like, I fought to get to where
I am, you know?
And, like, that same fight is,
like, now focused on you.
Like, I want to fight
for your love.
Like, I'ma do whatever it takes
to be that guy for you
at the end of the day.
- I believe you.
- Because I feel like
I'm in a place
where I can accept who I am
and give myself to someone.
And that's you, you know?
And like, just the little
jitters I got
just coming up the hall
and, like, you know,
the little--it just--
all these, like, feelings
and emotions, I've never felt
really for anyone.
You know, that's--
no one's ever
brought that much fire into me.
You know, like,
and that smile now, and--
all that, you know?
And I am falling hard.
Like, like, I really do
believe that.
So you know, I'm feeling
really strong about us.
I think, you know,
the world could be ours.
♪ ♪
- Um...
with that,
there are things I came in here
and that I know
that I'm looking for.
You know, not only are you
saying these things,
but also like, seeing how
your words and actions align,
it's just been really cool,
'cause every time, you've just
kind of like, blown me away.
I'm really excited about you,
and you were
exactly what I needed today.
So, Tyler, will you
accept this rose?
- Always.
Always.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hell yeah,
I'll accept that rose.
- Want to get out of here?
- Let's get out of here.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Oh, man.
I'm so happy right now.
I got you.
- You got me?
- I really
put a lot out there,
and I think she knows
how sincere I am.
Oh, man.
What a night.
Hannah and Tyler.
Goes well together.
- I--yeah.
I like it.
- That'll work.
[cheers and applause,
Hannah laughing]
[cheers and applause fade]
You know, it was
a big step forward for us.
And to get this rose
is an amazing feeling,
and it's--I'm getting one step
closer to Hannah's heart,
and I'ma keep
marching forward.
[cheers and applause]
[relaxing guitar music]
♪ ♪
- Hi!
[inaudible dialogue]
- ♪ Water towers
are made for ♪
♪ Hearts and names ♪
♪ And Friday nights
are made for ♪
- You know Jake Owen?
- Yeah.
all: ♪ Football games ♪
- Yes, sir.
- ♪ And falling leaves
are made for ♪
♪ Falling in ♪
♪ And front porch steps
are made for ♪
♪ Good night kissing ♪
♪ And I was made ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ For you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I was made ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Summer jobs are made for ♪
- Wow.
- ♪ Spending cash ♪
- Talk about feeling on top of
the world right now with you.
- ♪ Second dates
are made for ♪
♪ Obviously going fast ♪
[laughter]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I was made ♪
♪ For you ♪
- I'm just so happy.
She makes me feel way
different
than anyone's ever
made me feel before.
And to hear these lyrics
and be on this stage
with Hannah dancing--
I do believe that
we're made for each other,
and she could
be the one for sure.
- ♪ Yeah, I don't know
where I'd be ♪
♪ Or what I'd do ♪
- Oh, my God.
- ♪ Yeah, 'cause I ♪
all: ♪ Was made ♪
♪ For you ♪
- Today Tyler genuinely
wanted to be there for me,
and that is
what I'm looking for:
unconditional love.
It was super sweet.
Thank you.
- ♪ You were made to ♪
♪ Steal my heart ♪
♪ And I was made ♪
- [sighs]
- ♪ For you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I was made ♪
♪ For you ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Coming up...
- You kneed my partner
in the face while he was down.
- I did not.
- He is a master manipulator.
[dramatic music]
- This guy will do
just about anything
to screw you over.
- Really.
- Every bone in my body is
praying that Hannah sees it.
- Luke and Luke,
can I talk to y'all?
[dramatic music]
- Karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
♪ ♪
[waves crashing, birds calling]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- This is dope.
- This is insane, dude.
- Whoa!
Lions?
This is an alpha male's house.
- Wow.
No way.
Holy...
- Gotta go right.
♪ ♪
- Oh-ho-ho.
- Well, well, well,
well, well.
- Going to the cocktail party,
some of the guys
are a bit on edge
because of the Luke P. and
Luke S. feud the other night.
It sucks for Hannah
to have to, you know,
have all these emotions
going everywhere.
But tonight, hopefully,
there is no drama.
And I can't wait to continue
building a connection
with her.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I'll say this.
Just going forward,
I just think
let's continue
to be ourselves
and, you know,
I think it's very important
to make sure
we're very truthful
with everything that we say.
And with that being said,
you know, this is definitely
about Hannah.
No doubt about it.
- I'm still upset
with Luke P. right now--
to be cheap shot body-slammed
and having my character
questioned.
But my job is to continue
my relationship with her,
not to talk about Luke P.
So, looking forward to
setting things straight
with Hannah tonight.
♪ ♪
- Hey, y'all.
- Hi.
- How is everybody?
[all murmur indistinctly]
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
This week has been a hard week.
It's made me question
some of people's character.
You know,
all I've asked for is just
for everyone to be real with me
and that I would
be that in return.
So I am excited for tonight
and hopeful
to get more clarity.
Let's have a great night,
and continue on this crazy,
fun journey to love together.
So, cheers.
- Cheers.
[glasses clinking]
- I hope that we can just
enjoy the cocktail party
tonight
and talk about Hannah more than
we talk about the Lukes.
Tonight is just
another opportunity
to get some good time
with Hannah.
I really see potential
with this,
so I just want to
keep that energy going,
that momentum going.
You're so friggin' beautiful.
- You're so sweet.
- No, but it's true.
And I know that
this is, like, not the way
this goes normally...
- Mm-hmm.
- But
I just want to
ask you something.
- Okay.
- I guess. Um...
- Oh, God. What?
- I'm like--I'm like,
hyping this up
way too much right now.
- I'm like, "Well...
Well,
what are you asking me?"
- I just--
I believe that, like,
being, like, intentional
and, like, direct
in a relationship's
very important.
So I wanted to, like,
officially ask...
- [laughs]
- If you wanted to
be my girlfriend.
I know--I'll--I'll--
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'll preface it with
I'm okay with you dating,
like, 14 other guys
at the same time, but--
- I would love to be your
girlfriend.
- Would you?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Man.
- We made that official.
I've got a girlfriend.
All right.
I like it.
- I have a boyfriend.
- Look at that.
- But, like,
plus 14.
- Plus 14.
That's okay.
I understand--
- But only one boyfriend
who actually asked me.
- Am I the first one?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, well, that counts
for something.
- Oh, it definitely counts.
- I like that.
- I like it.
- This is happening fast
for me, but
I don't know.
I just--
I have such a good feeling
and, like,
[sighs]
I'm ready.
You know?
I'm--I'm gonna give it my all.
So...
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm just very excited to see
where this goes.
- News flash:
Peter's my boyfriend.
And we're dating.
♪ ♪
I love talking to Peter.
I love making out with Peter
even more.
Ruffled up my hair a little
bit, and I'm all about it.
I'm excited about the future
and where this can go.
So it was nice
that he grabbed me first
so I could start off
the night really strong.
- Like, what's up?
- Do you think Luke P.'s
getting a rose?
- I think he will.
- Uh, yeah.
He probably will.
- You think he will?
- Yeah.
- It's very possible that
I will be going home tonight,
based off false information
that has continued
to be fed to her by him.
So...
we'll see what happens.
- I have three queens
back home:
My younger sister, my mother,
and my grandmother.
And I really started to
like you more.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I could see you
being my fourth and last queen.
And I didn't like some things
that took place this week,
'cause it made you
feel a certain way.
- Mm-hmm.
- Last Rose Ceremony,
you shed a tear, and it...
I was like, "Whoa," you know?
'Cause I--of course, I don't
want to see a woman cry.
- Mm-hmm.
It is very, very,
very important to me
that the men
that are truly here for me,
that trust me and, like,
know I'm taking everything
so seriously
because I do care,
and to trust that.
That's what all I can ask for.
You know?
- Absolutely.
I find myself
stepping up for Hannah
when I think someone
has bad intentions.
I know you're gonna
follow your heart.
And through action,
I'm starting to like you
more and more.
I'm here for Hannah.
But we have all this drama
going on in the house.
And I don't know
if Hannah sees it.
I do feel like
there's a blind spot.
But I just read through the BS,
and I hit you straight.
- I was telling Mike earlier,
I was like,
"If, for some reason,
Luke P. gets a rose,
in my eyes, that's diminishing
the value of the rose."
That's giving him affirmation
that everything he's
been doing--that's okay.
- I just want Hannah happy,
and I hope that she sees that.
- Yeah.
- So that's what that is.
Uh...
- [grunts]
- Have you spoken to her?
- To Hannah?
No.
- So everybody knows
I'm outspoken.
And I'm pissed off
with the fact
that the actions
of a few days ago,
it's still lingering,
and I'm for one, you know,
don't want to have that.
And you and I both know
for a fact,
despite how you
think that you feel,
you're the cause of her not
being her happiest right now.
- Actually...
I'm not the cause.
Luke S. is actually
the cause of that,
because of the whole situation.
- You kneed my partner
in the face while he was down.
You can't even do that in UFC.
- I did not.
- But wasn't the ball--
- Listen.
- Wasn't the ball
on the other side of the field?
- He's on his back right here,
and I'm straddling him.
I have my eyes
over at the game,
and I step over him.
It was a piece
of, like, my shin
that caught his shoulder
and maybe part of his ear.
So you can take that...
and flush it,
because you were never there
and you didn't see it
with your own eyes.
- I know what Dustin said,
and Dustin was on the bench
the entire time.
I know what the audience's
action was.
I know what Hannah's face was.
- You're telling me
the sky is red,
but I'm telling you,
I've seen it; I know it's blue.
- You're a [bleep] dumbass now.
Because the [bleep] sky's
not red.
- You're telling me
you know something;
you didn't even
see what happened.
- You are a millennial
[bleep].
That's what you acting like,
and that's what you are.
I don't think you right
for Hannah.
You, time and time again,
are the issue.
You are aggressive.
You are abnormally violent.
You scheme about things.
You have lied about things.
- I've done
absolutely nothing negative
or disrespectful
to anybody in the house.
- Your character has shown
that you're unstable.
You are a psychopath.
That's who you are.
- This is the definition
of psychopath.
That's the complete opposite
of me.
- I think that you're trying to
be methodical.
I think that you went after
Luke S. for a reason.
- This man clenches his fists
while he's, like,
cussing me out,
and to me,
I genuinely thought
I was defending myself,
because--
- Luke? You defending yourself
against Luke S.?
You gonna grab somebody,
come after me, homie.
You damn sure
won't go after me.
I feel like you think
that I'm a threat to you,
'cause I am the biggest threat
against you right now.
- I'm not threatened
by anybody,
especially not you.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- I think we all know that
you're here
for the right reasons.
- Yeah.
I-I don't want this
to be the focal point
of the night,
but I mean, it is what it is,
you know?
- I mean, I didn't even know
you had a tequila business
or company or whatever.
- Ha.
I know.
- I at least want to do
everything I can--
you know, 'cause I care
about her and I like her
and I want to see
where this goes.
But at the end of the day,
I want to try everything I can
to, like, make it known
as to what the truth is,
and that's how I feel about it.
It's definitely been a rough--
a rough week for me.
Ever since the rugby game,
it's sort of
been a downward spiral.
So I hope that tonight I can
have a good conversation
with Hannah
and set the ship
straight again.
I really think
that she is a great woman
who really is
a good fit for me,
and I hope to be able
to continue on
in getting
to know her better.
Um,
I was taken aback by
the conversation
that happened between us.
My character is of the utmost
importance to me.
It's like the most important
thing about me,
and it being,
like, called into question
made the last few days,
like, incredibly hard.
- Mm-hmm.
- I grew up with two parents
that were social workers,
and they raised me to have
the highest, like, moral fiber.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I'm sorry if
you ever felt or even if you--
I don't know
if you still feel like
my intentions
are in question...
- Yeah.
- And I wanted to hear you
on that.
- Um, the night
of the group date
just was really,
really hard for me.
And yes, I know that
there are other men here
that don't, you know,
get along with Luke P.
And I mean, I've definitely
been a part of
my own drama being here,
so, like, I get it.
But I see kind of--
but I see both sides.
And so I'm still
just trying to, like,
work out my emotions
right now...
- Absolutely.
- And...
I'm at a point
where I just, like,
don't know
who to trust in things.
Because I'm confused,
but also, like, irritated.
But irritated in, like,
completely different ways
between, like, both of you.
'Cause it's hard on me.
So...
I don't know.
[dramatic chords]
- That conversation was
a little alarming for me.
And I think that
she's siding with Luke P.
And it stinks that
sharing a passion of mine,
something that I'm very
excited about in the future
is considered self-promotion.
Because it's just not true.
It's not true.
Yeah, Luke,
I'm gonna be honest here.
She doesn't trust me.
And it was because of what you
said about the tequila thing,
which is complete crap.
You really think
I'm here for that?
- I mean, out of everyone
here--
- Luke, yes or no, man?
- No.
- Are you gonna tell her
that you feel that way?
- Yeah, I plan on it.
I plan on telling her
that I do believe
that you are here
for the right reasons.
'Cause guess what.
She's questioning my character.
And I don't--
I didn't ever want her
to be in a position
like that from me.
And so I can total--I totally
understand how you feel.
- But you can't just
go to her and say,
"Hey, actually Luke S. is here
for the right reasons."
You need to go to her and say,
"What I said about Luke S.
was wrong.
I was wrong."
- Okay.
- All right.
All right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- This is about
Luke P. doing what's right
while he still has a chance
to do something right.
And simple as that.
♪ ♪
- I know this has been
a rough week,
for the both of us.
And I don't ever
want to be the guy
that makes you have to
go on
an emotional roller coaster.
Like, that's the last thing
I want you to go through,
especially with me.
And the last person I want to
talk about right now
is Luke S.,
but he came up to me,
like, asking me
to put in a good word
for him to you,
which I have no business
concerning myself with.
But what I want you to know
is, you know,
what I told you
the other night about him,
you know, my opinion about
him being here
for the right reasons--
although he tried to
talk me into thinking
that he is here
for the right reasons--
Nothing has changed.
♪ ♪
- The last time that I was
on a group date
with the two Lukes,
Luke S. was talking
about how just terrible
and reckless and a monster
Luke P. is.
And then tonight,
he wants Luke P.
to speak on his behalf.
That doesn't make sense.
So I need to get to the bottom
of everything.
[crickets chirping]
So I'm just trying to
figure out,
like, what's going on.
Because Luke said to me
that you just wanted him
to kind of like talk you up
and, like, clear the air
in a way.
And, like,
I guess it's just like--
- It wasn't to talk me up,
it was to tell the truth.
- But my issue is that, like,
you asked for him to, like...
- Listen.
- Talk about you.
- I didn't ask for him
to do that.
I didn't ask for him
I basically--I--
I'm trying
to clear the air here
because I wasn't forcing him
to do anything.
All I want in the situation
is for you to have
the truth of the matter.
And that's all I want.
- I have to unpack my thoughts
a little bit more.
Because I don't know.
- All right, that's fine.
- Okay.
Luke P. is a lying,
manipulative piece of [bleep].
And every bone in my body
is praying that Hannah sees it
and sees him
for the piece of crap he is.
Hannah basically expressed
to me that I had told you
to go upstairs
and say good things about me.
Why would you frame it as,
"Luke told me
to come tell you"?
Why would you do that?
You understand what that does
when you go up there
and you say, "Luke forced me
to come up here
and tell you good things
about him."
- Okay, I didn't--
I didn't say to her I--she--
that you forced me.
I said that you were--
- Had told me to tell you.
It's the same concept.
It's all the same concept.
And, guys, I want you to be
warned.
This guy right here, he's good.
This guy will do just about
anything to screw you over.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Did you or did you not,
though,
ask me on my behalf
to tell her?
- You know exactly what
the [bleep] you did, man.
You said it in front of us,
dude, like--
- You said it in front of us.
I said to you,
"Please go up there
and tell her the truth."
Did I not say that to you?
- I did nothing but that.
- Damn it, dude.
- Am I crazy here?
- No.
- You're not--
you're not crazy.
He said it
in front of everybody.
Just--you said it
- No, but around the corner,
not in front of everyone,
my man here asked me
on my behalf--
- That's total [bleep], dude.
Like--
- It's crazy, man.
Honestly.
- That's--that is
so [bleep] unbelievable.
- I didn't think
you had it in you.
I can't believe I got
outsmarted by you.
I am so angry at myself.
- At the end of the day--
- For letting this happen.
Let me just tell you, man,
karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
Trust me.
[dramatic music]
- Luke and Luke,
can I talk to y'all?
♪ ♪
- I've never disliked anyone
more in my entire life.
♪ ♪
- He is a master manipulator.
It's simple as that.
- She's a tough cookie,
and she means business.
And I dig it.
I trust that in the end,
she'll make the right call.
- I'm really confused,
so I just want to hear you guys
talk to each other about this.
What's going on?
[dramatic music]
- Next week
on "The Bachelorette"...
♪ ♪
- If I was Luke P.,
I would be very nervous.
- You want to make sure that
she chooses the right guy.
- The woman of my dreams
is slipping out of my fingers,
and I'm at
the breaking point.
- Whoa.
- No.
- The beast is gonna come out.
- This is war!
[men screaming]
- I'm about to
fight for Hannah right now.
- I need to show my queen
that I could be her king.
- [laughing]
- I'm coming here
to win Hannah's heart,
and I don't like to lose.
- This is about
me caring about Hannah;
not letting some little snake
slide his way into her heart
and her mind.
- It's all coming up next week
on "The Bachelorette."
[percussive music]
♪ ♪
- Yeah!
- Oh, snap.
♪ ♪
- Ooh!
[laughter]
♪ ♪
- Oh, cash!
- Yeah!
- Give him some cash!
Yeah, give him some cash!
- Some cash!
- Yeah, give him some cash!
♪ ♪
- Yes, I made some money!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Give him lots of money!
[laughter]
♪ ♪
- Yes, I made some money!
- He made some money!
- Yeah!
- Hey.
♪ ♪
- Yes, I made some more money!
- Whoo!